<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<knimeNode icon="./default.png" type="Source" xmlns="http://knime.org/node/v2.8" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://knime.org/node/v2.8 http://knime.org/node/v2.8.xsd">
    <name>OPS_Swagger</name>
    
    <shortDescription>
        This node loads a swagger web service description file and lets the user select on of the services via the config panel together with setting default parameters. An input table can be added with more parameters and values. The result of executing the node is a URL with the service call. 
    </shortDescription>
    
    <fullDescription>
        <intro>Via the config panel the user provides the URL to a swagger file. Once the fetch button is clicked a number of services described
        in the loaded swagger appear in a drop-down list. The 'parameters' tab appears after loading and shows the parameters that will hold the
        default parameter settings for that service. The input table overwrites the values accordingly. The result of this service is a (hopefully)
        executable REST url composed of the parameters and service that is selected. 
      </intro>
        
        <tab name="Swagger URL settings">
        	<option name="Swagger URL">provide the swagger url here</option>
        	<option name="Select Service">after successfully fetching the swagger file, a list of services appear in this drop-down list. The parameter tab will show the parameters that are available for the selected service</option>
     	 </tab>
        <tab name="Service selection parameters">
            <option name="parameter names and default values">One can specify the default settings for the parameters. For example, an application verification key. Note that the parameter values in the input table will overwrite these default parameters</option>
        </tab>
        
        
    </fullDescription>
    
    <ports>
        <inPort index="0" name="Parameters">A table with one row. The column headers are the parameter names and the each corresponding cell 
        on the first row (rest of the rows are ignored)</inPort>
        <!-- possibly more input ports here-->
        <outPort index="0" name="executable URL">A table with one cell containing he result service call URL based on the selected service and the parameters. </outPort>
        <!-- possibly more output ports here-->
    </ports>    
    <views>
        <view index="0" name="name of first view">Description of first view...</view>
        <!--view index="1" name="name of second view">Description of second view...</view-->
    </views>
</knimeNode>
