<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<knimeNode icon="./default.png" type="Source" xmlns="http://knime.org/node/v2.8" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://knime.org/node/v2.8 http://knime.org/node/v2.8.xsd">
    <name>OPS_JSON</name>
    
    <shortDescription>
        Reads JSON from a URL and transforms the result into  KNIME tables
    </shortDescription>
    
    <fullDescription>
        <intro>Reads JSON from a URL provided by the input table and creates two tables. The first table is a user specified selection
        of the json result where the user specified the desired JSON path keys via the option panel. The second table is the fully
        serialized JSON result. The option panel needs an example JSON file for which it automatically derives the JSON keys that
        the user can select. </intro>
        
        
        <option name="JSON example URL">Provide a URL to a JSON result that contains all the keys that you expect from the
        JSON url that will arrive from the node input.</option>
        <option name="JSON key selection">Select the key that you want to have in the first output table. The key will become the column header. You can change
        the column header by typing a new name in the textfield next to the parameter option.</option>
        <!-- possibly more options that can also be grouped by tabs -->
        <!--
        <tab name="Standard Options">
            <option name="short name of first option (like in the dialog)">description of first option</option>
            <option name="short name of second option (like in the dialog)">description of second option</option>
        </tab>
        <tab name="Advanced Options">
            <option name="short name of first advanced option (like in the dialog)">description of first advanced option</option>
        </tab>
        -->
    </fullDescription>
    
    <ports>
        <inPort index="0" name="JSON url">A table with one cell containing the url to the JSON data. Make sure that the column header is named 'url'</inPort>
        <!-- possibly more input ports here-->
        <outPort index="0" name="JSON selection">Result of the parsed JSON filtered by user-specified key selection and custom column headers</outPort>
        <outPort index="1" name="JSON complete">Complete JSON result, ignoring the selection settings from the user</outPort>
        <!-- possibly more output ports here-->
    </ports>    
    <views>
        <view index="0" name="name of first view">Description of first view...</view>
        <!--view index="1" name="name of second view">Description of second view...</view-->
    </views>
</knimeNode>
